Dragon Slayer?
Yes.
There are evil dragons
that do mean things to people.
They're called Devil Dragons.
Oh!
This adventurer slayed one
by cutting its head off.
Then the scales, claws, fangs,
and bones
were all turned into materials for high
quality weapons and medicines,
which brought wealth to the land.
Wow...
That made the adventurer a hero
who people called the "Dragon Slayer."
I wanna be one too!
I wanna be a Dragon Slayer hero!
That's no easy task.
Some dragons are incredibly strong ones
that have lived for thousands of years.
They can make the ground tremble
just by walking,
and even crumble mountains
by swinging their tails.
In fact,
this continent was almost destroyed
long ago by dragons that ran wild.
They'd chomp on kids like you for a snack!
Hm? What is that?
What's wrong?
I have a feeling something's out there.
I don't see anything.
You don't?
It's right there.
That's...
a Dragon of Calamity...
I don't believe it.
Does the empire understand
the horror they've unleashed?!
According to the records,
it's been only 150 years
since it fell asleep.
It should be in its
dormant period right now.
They awakened it?!
The damn fools!
Who resorts to using something
so destructive in a simple dispute?!
Round up everyone
who took shelter in the capital
and have them evacuate immediately!
And I mean all of them!
If they try to stay, carry them out!
And peel them away from their belongings
if they cling to them!
Don't leave a single person
in the capital!
I'm sensing more magic that's being used
to obstruct all the evacuation routes.
So it's basically impossible now...
for the Sovereign Six to unite.
Damn these nuisances!
Your Majesty!
You must leave and take refuge!
We won't stand a chance
when that thing gets here!
I want you warriors to protect the people.
Focus on guiding them
away from the capital.
I still have my own job to take care of.
In the face of that dragon,
there's no doubt the capital
will be absolutely destroyed.
They should be evacuating everyone by now.
If so, then my father...
He'll surely choose
to use himself as a shield.
But then...
Yeah.
Even my father is no match
for something like that.
Please leave, Father.
A dragon, huh?
So that's how big they are.
This is the first time
I'm seeing a real one.
Huh? It is?
The Black Death Dragon
was a dragon as well, though...
Lynne, are your brother
and father still in the city?
Yes.
I have no doubt they've stayed behind.
But, it's too late for us to help them.
No, I think I can do it, if I run.
Run?
Despite how far away we are?
Yeah.
Remember what we did against that goblin?
I think that would work here.
You mean the Wind Blast?
I mean, that is an option,
but it's going to hit you pretty hard...
This sword will take the brunt of it.
I owe a lot to the people
of that city and your dad.
So I'd like to lend a hand.
Helping him escape shouldn't be too hard.
I think I can handle that.
Yeah. I suppose you could.
What am I sitting here
being pessimistic for?
My instructor says he can make it in time.
Wind Blast is not normally a spell
that's used on people.
But this is one person
who I shouldn't try to measure
with my limited knowledge.
There's no need to hesitate.
That's what you're telling me, right?
Huh?
Crushing your puny country
with brute force is a simple task.
No matter what you may say,
I cannot hand the Dungeon of the Lost
over to you.
You bastards are just
letting it go to waste.
But with the intelligence of our empire,
it could be a military power
strong enough to control the world.
Don't you get it?
We merely chose not to use a power
that's beyond our control.
You can see the logic in that, can't you?
That is why you will always remain
the king of a small nation.
You have never had it in you to be a king.
He cares about nothing else
as long as he gets the dungeon, huh?
I underestimated him.
I never expected he would throw the
full force of his might at us like this.
Letting negotiations break down
was a mistake on my part.
Father!
The capital faces certain doom,
and yet all I can think about
is my daughter's safety?
Some leader I am.
Never had it in me to be king, huh?
That's exactly right.
I've always been more suited
to being on the battlefield.
I am truly sorry to
the people of this country
who have obeyed their foolish king.
It won't be enough
to make amends for my sins,
but at the very least,
I'm going to take
one of its damn eyes with me.
Divine Shield.
Sir Noor, stand in front of this cylinder.
Huh? Uh, yeah.
Magic Barrier.
Reflect.
Magic Reflect.
Enhance.
What's this?
Charge. Burst!
This seems different from the last time...
Condense.
Okay, here we go.
The impact from this is going to be
far stronger than it was before.
Apologies in advance!
Huh, uh, hold o-
Multi-cast!
I've put literally
everything that I have into this.
Six-fold Cast!
Wind Blast!
Instructor...
Godspeed.
Is that...
the elder dragon breath
that burned this continent to a crisp
several hundred years ago?!
So, it won't even give me
the chance to retaliate, huh?
But I've got to do something kingly
at least once in the end!
Come get me, elder dragon!
You're going to learn a painful lesson
about how tenacious we humans are!
The Blasting Sword.
It channels all of the wielder's mana
in one powerful, sacrificial blow.
So, he's sacrificing himself.
Come!
Parry!
Why?
Why am I covered in a cloud of dust?
Is this why? This little person?
He got in my way?
The strong control the weak
and crush them with violence.
That is the natural law of this world.
And any who dare oppose it...
shall fall!
Parry!
I thought I was gonna die.
Six-fold Cast!
Wind Blast!
Physical Enhancement!
Man, that was a close call!
The castle walls?!
Ah, the dragon...
It was so far away just a moment ago.
Oh no! I can't stop myself!
I'm gonna run into it!
Parry!
Well, I made it through in one piece...
But I'm telling Lynne
we're never doing that again.
Anyways...
That was easier to parry than I expected.
It's shocking how huge
this dragon actually is,
but the impact from Lynne's magic
really threw me for a loop.
So actually...
this doesn't seem so scary.
Right now...
Even I...
might be able to fight this thing!
There's so much damage...
Yes.
Let's find the king and
escape this place quickly
while Sir Noor fights the elder dragon.
Watch out!
Lady Lynneburg!
You saved my life, Ines.
Please stay close to me.
Goblin Emperors?!
They're quite small compared
to the one Noor and I confronted.
But it doesn't change the fact
that Goblin Emperors
are monsters in a league of their own.
How should we fight them?
I need to start thinking
like Instructor Noor does.
Ines, we've nothing to be afraid of.
We're only fighting mere goblins.
Indeed.
Compared to that dragon,
these really are just plain goblins.
Let's keep our cool and handle this.
Icicle Dance!
So fast!
I'm sorry.
Stay put. Don't move a muscle.
They stopped moving!
Cocytus!
Divine Sword!
That's Ines for you.
Not only do people
call her the "Divine Shield,"
but she's more than worthy
of her "Divine Sword" title, too.
And Rolo...
I saw him stop those huge goblins
with just a few words.
Demonfolk are unbelievable.
The fact this young boy
has such power is crazy.
But even then...
I can tell it takes him
great courage to use.
Let's hurry!
This makes no sense!
Parry!
My claws and scales
should be indestructible!
How are they getting so
badly damaged?!
I swear this thing
never gets a single scratch!
No matter what I swing it at!
Seriously, what is the deal
with this sword?
But whatever.
It's my key to victory!
Something is wrong here.
But no matter, because there
is no way that this attack can fail.
Parry!
Did he just parry
the elder dragon's breath?
Instructor!
It's angry...
Huh?
But that's not all.
The dragon's frustrated because Noor
isn't treating it as a serious threat,
even though that's what it's trying to be.
Dragons are very prideful beasts.
Especially the Elder Dragon,
which believes it's more powerful
than anything.
But, watching this fight,
it's almost like...
The one who is weak...
The one who is small...
is me, isn't it?!
Parry!
It seems like it's calmed down...
Uh, I think...
it's actually submitting to him.
What's going on?
Oh, look...
The scales, claws, fangs, and bones
were all turned into materials for
high quality weapons and medicines,
which brought wealth to the land.
That made the adventurer a hero
who people called the "Dragon Slayer."
Well, shucks.
I really don't think
I'm hero material.
It looks like it doesn't want
to fight anymore.
Instructor Noor!
Instructor!
#8 I Parry a Dragon